Guide to the Vice President and Secretary Administrative Records 1925-1965 RG 4.0.1
New York University Libraries, Publisher
- Series I: Administrative Correspondence and Subject Files Container List
  - Discrimination in Admissions (N.Y. State), Division of General Education, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Division of General Education, 1926-1960 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ea - Ez Miscellaneous, 1935-1936; , undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Education, School of: Correspondence, 1933-1961 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Education, School of: Printed material, 1937-1961 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Education, School of: Negotiations with Outdoor Education Inc., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Education for Defence (Bulletin), 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Educational Services, Office of: Ray F. Harvey (Director), 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Educational Television: Reports and Bulletins, 1946-1954 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Educational Television: Printed Material, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Employee Remission, 1946-1953 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Employment, Bureau of, 1942-1952 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Encyclopedia Americana, 1957; , 1959 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Engineering, College of, 1933-1958 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Engineering, College of: Correspondence and Printed Material, 1935-1964 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Engineering, College of: Proposal to organize an Institute of Technology, 1946-1951 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Exploratory Committee on Financing Higher Education and Research/, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Fa - Fz Miscellaneous, 1930-1957; , undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Faculty, Miscellaneous, 1940-1960 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Club: Minutes of Executive Committee/ Correspondence, 1933-1960 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Committee on Recruitment: Memoranda, Reports, and Minutes, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Directory, 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Exchange (Institute of International Education): Questionnaires, 1954-1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Health Services Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Salaries Study, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Salaries: Correspondence regarding payment of first bonus to staff, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Salaries: Correspondence regarding payment of second bonus to staff, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Salaries: Correspondence regarding payment of third bonus to staff, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Faculty financial position and bonus study, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Tenure, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Federal Aid for Education: Printed Material, 1947-1950 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Federal Emergency Relief Administration, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Fee Structure: Administrative Committee to Study Procedures Effecting Changes, 1958-1961 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Fee Structure: Faculty Committee, 1958-1961 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Fees: Memoranda (by Schools and misc.), 1944-1959 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Fees: General Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Fees: Protest, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Fees, General Increases, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Fees, General Increases, 1952-1960 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Fees, Miscellaneous, 1935-1937 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Fees, Miscellaneous, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Fees, Miscellaneous, 1939-1943; , undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Fine Arts/ College of, 1926-1958 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Financial Campaign: Printed Material, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Ford Foundation Report: Biographies for, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Students, University Committee for: Memoranda, Minute s, 1954-1957 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Ga - Gz Miscellaneous, 1931-1958 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin College, Proposed Establishment of: Critiques and Drafts, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Gallery of Living Art, 1931; , 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Glover, John G., 1941; , 1943 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Gould House at Ardley: Miscellaneous, 1954-1961 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Gould Student Center: Annual Reports, Food Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration: Minutes and Memoranda, 1952-1960 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Greenwich House/, 1946; , 1948 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Grisewood, E. N. (Director of University Broadcasts), 1946-1948 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Grisewood, E. N.: Report, 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Ha - Hz Miscellaneous, 1929-1955 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Hamilton, Samual L. (Professor of Education), 1929; , 1940; , 1953 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Hofstra College (Nassau College): Correspondence, 1937-1940 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Holt, Mrs. L. Emmett Jr.: Prospectus on possible TV series, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Honorary Society, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Howley, Frank L. (Director, Office of Military Government, Berlin Sector), 1945-1946; , 1949 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Hudson Celebration (350th Anniversary of Discovery of Hudson River): Bulletins, Mimeos, and Minutes, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - la - Iz Miscellaneous, 1942-1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Information Services, Office of, 1952-1954 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Inter-Atlantic Relations, 1945-1946 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Institute for the Crippled and Disabled: Printed material, clippings, 1950-1960 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Mathematics and Mechanics: Correspondence and reports, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Institute of Comparative Law, 1953-1961 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Institute of Disaster Prevention and Control: Correspondence and Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Institute of Fine Arts, 1937; , 1939 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Institute of Urbanism, 1937; , 1939 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Institutional Research, Office of: Reports and Studies, 1959-1961 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Inventions and Patents Committee: Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Israel Program (NYU's Program in Israel): Progress Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Ja - Jz Miscellaneous, 1937-1948 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Joint Programs of NYU with other Institutions: Correspondence, 1953-1961 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Jones, Theodore F., 1925- 1956 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Journalism Department: Accreditation Committee: Correspondence and Report, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Judson Dormitory, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Judson Property, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Ka - Kz Miscellaneous, 1944-1946 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Kastner, Elmer C. (Association of Colleges and University of the State of New York), 1948 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Keston, Albert S-, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Kimball, Leroy E., 1928-1950 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - La - Lz Miscellaneous, 1928-1953 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Labor Relations, Committee on: Correspondence, Minutes and Memoranda, 1937-1945 (Box 14, Folder 8-10)
  - LaGuardia Hall Mural: Correspondence, Clippings, 1933-1949 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Law, School of, 1935-1943 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Lindberg, Charles A- (Committee For the Celebration of the Tenth Anniversary), 1937 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Loeb Student Center: Correspondence, 1955-1958 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Loeb Student Center: Committee Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Loeb Student Center: General Program Director (Amanda Caldwell), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Loeb Student Center: Governance of, 1955-1958 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Loeb Student Center: Student Union Planning Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Ma - Mz Miscellaneous, 1931-1961 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Mathias, Leon L.: Proposal to establish NYU branch in Lugano, Switzerland, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - McGhee, Paul A. (Dean, Division of General Education): Addresses, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Medical Care, University Senate Committee on, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda, 1930-1961 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Na - Nz Miscellaneous, 1930-1958 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Nathan/ Otto, 1933-1959 (Box 15, Folder 15-16)
  - National Academy of Design, 1933; , 1936 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - National Arts Center, 1952-1956 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - National Commission for Cooperative Education, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - National Committee for Free Europe, Inc., 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - National Youth Administration, 1935; , 1940; , 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Newell, James Michael (Muralist), 1934 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - New York Institute of Credit, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - New York Law School, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - New York School of Social Work, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - New York State Aid to Education, Proposal for (A Scholar Incentive Program), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - NYU: Plans for a Motion Picture, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - New York University Medical Center, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - New York University Press: Correspondence, 1937-1950 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - New York University Press: Notice of Meetings and Minutes, 1946-1950 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - New York University Social Science Field Laboratory, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Oa - Oz Miscellaneous, 1931-1961 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Ochoa, Dr. Severo, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Officer's Meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Offner, Richard (Professor, Fine Arts Graduate Center), 1935 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Onderdonk, Chester D. (Director of Plant and Properties, University Heights), 1928-1935; , 1961 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - "Overseas Information Services: A New Career" Conference on, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Pa - Pz Miscellaneous/, 1926-1954 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Panel of Americans, 1955-1959 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Paris, W. Francklyn (Founder, The Hall of American Artists, University Heights), 1930-1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Parsons School of Design, 1954-1955; , 1961 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Personnel Directives, including Personnel Manual Material, 1944-1946; , 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Personnel Division, 1943-1961 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Phelps and Stokes Lectures: Program brochures, 1951; , 1955; , 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Placement Services: Mergers, 1939-1941; , 1952 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Planning Committee: General Correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Planning Committee: School of Education-Outdoor Education Proposal, Fund Raising, 1949-1950 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Planning Committee: Washington Square College-Dreyfus Foundation, 1949-1950 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Plants and Properties, Plant Protection, 1957-1961 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Pohl, Frederick V., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Political Groups at New York University: Students for America, Labor Youth League, Young Socialist league, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Post-War Reconstruction, Institute of: General Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 18, Folder 2-6)
  - Power House and Educational Building, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Property, Supervisor of, 1930-1953 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Protestant Center, Proposed Establishment of: Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 9-12)
  - Protestant Center, Proposed Establishment of: Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Psychological Research Center, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Director of: Kelvin A. Arden, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Publications and Printing, 1930-1959 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
  - Public Relations: Voorhis Study of 1950: (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - Public Relations, University Committee on, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Quigley, John, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Ra - Rz Miscellaneous, 1932-1961; , undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Racial and Religious Statistics, 1941-1953 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Radiation Laboratory, M.I.T., 1945 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Radio Committee, 1939-1945 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Radio Station WMCA Proposal, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Refugee Instructors on University Staff, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Refugee Scholarships: Correspondence with students, 1939-1941 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Report to the Council Committee on Scholarships, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Research at New York University, 1931-1935; , 1960; , undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Residence Bureau, 1926-1927 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - ROTC Activities, 1939-1961 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
  - Sa - Sz Miscellaneous, 1929-1961 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Sailor's Snug Harbor Property (Washington Square North), 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Savage School, 1943; , 1949 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Scholarship Memorandum, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Scholarship Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Scholarship Inquiry/ Committee on the, 1926-1930; , undated (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Scholarship Study, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Scholarships, 1929-1930 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Scholarships, 1940; , 1943; , 1953 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Sloan Foundation, 1951-1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Rufus D., (Provost and Dean, Washington Square College): Correspondence, 1928-1949 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Rufus D., (Provost and Dean, Washington Square College): Correspondence, 1950-1954 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Rufus D., (Provost and Dean, Washington Square College): Memorial Committee, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Rufus D., (Provost and Dean, Washington Square College): Trends in College enrollments: Materials, 1947-1948 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Social Research Center, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Social Security Legislation, 1950-1951 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Social Service Program, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Society for the Libraries of New York Uni ver.si hv., 1938-1945 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Society of Independent Motion Picture Producers, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Special Services to Business and Industry, Office of, 1954-1957 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Square Playhouse of NYU, 1952-1958 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - State University of New York: General Correspondence, 1948-1957 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - State University of New York: Expansion Plans for Long Island, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Steiner-Prag, Hugo, 1940-1947 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Stessin, Lawrence: NYU-Israel Program, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Student Affairs and Activities, Student Unions, Protest, 1934-1937; , 1941 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Students, Dean of: Elwood C. Kastner, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Student Activities, Non-Athletic, 1947-1958 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Student Health (and Medical Care of Students), 1934-1945 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Student Orientation Programs, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Student Service (Ghost Writing of Student Theses), 1940-1941 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Student Service Organization, 1952-1960 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Student Union: Conversion of Army Mess Hall, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Summer Session Planning Committee, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Summer Session in Europe, 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Ta - Tz Miscellaneous, 1933-1953 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Testing and Advisement Center, 1945-1952 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Television Committee, 1945-1948 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Tompkins, Leslie, 1937-1946 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Town Hall, 1956-1960 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Tuition Remission, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Ua - Uz Miscellaneous, 1940-1958 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Athletic Board, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - United States House Un-American Activities Committee, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - University Heights, Joint Program, 1955; , 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - University of the State of New York, 1931-1955 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - University of the State of New York: Television Courses, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Va - Vz Miscellaneous, 1937; , 1958 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Vice President for Business Affairs and Treasurer (George F. Baughman), 1956-1961 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Vice President for University Development, 1957-1960; , undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Visiting Committee for University Heights, 1951-1952 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Wa - "Wz Miscellaneous, 1927-1961 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Wallace Clark International Management Center, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Washington Square College, 1949-1950; , 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Washington Square Property: General, 1949-1960 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Washington Square Property: Community Protests, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Washington Square Property: Main Building, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Washington Square Property: #2 Washington Square North, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Washington Square Property: 61 Washington Square South ("Genius Row"), 1948 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Washington Square Property: Washington Square Southeast: Redevelopment Project (Faculty and student housing), 1953-1961 (Box 24, Folder 20-21)
  - Westchester Center, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Who's Who, 1946-1947 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Wolfe, Thomas, 1949-1958 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - World Cruise Project, 1926-1928 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - World University -Service, 1953-1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - World War II Activities: Correspondence requesting reports for history, 1946-1947 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - World War II Activities: Army Specialized Training Program (ASTP), Naval Training Programs, 1945-1947 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - World War II Activities: Reports: Alumni Office, College of Engineering, Public Occasions, Provost, and Registrar's Offices, 1946-1947 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - World War II Activities: Reports: School of Law - War Service Record, 1941-1945, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - World War II Activities: Reports: Center for Safety Education, 1942-1946 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - World's Fair, 1938-1940 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous, 1941; , 1945 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - YMCA: Intercollegiate Branch, 1936-1940 (Box 25, Folder 13-16)
  - YMCA: Intercollegiate Branch:, 1940-1947 (Box 26, Folder 1-7)
  - YMCA: Intercollegiate Branch, Secretaryship vacancy, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - YMCA: World Youth Fund, 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - YMCA Special Committee for the Study of Quarters and Equipment needs: General Committee Material, 1939-1944 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - YMCA Special Committee for the Study of Quarters and Equipment needs: Hanford, John M., 1944 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - YMCA Special Committee for the Study of Quarters and Equipment needs: Minutes, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - YMCA Special Committee for the Study of Quarters and Equipment needs: Questionnaires: Chancellor Chase, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - YMCA Special Committee for the Study of Quarters and Equipment needs: Questionnaires: Columbia University, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - YMCA Special Committee for the Study of Quarters and Equipment needs: Questionnaires: CCNY Downtown Branch, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - YMCA Special Committee for the Study of Quarters and Equipment needs: Questionnaires: CCNY Uptown Branch, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - YMCA Special Committee for the Study of Quarters and Equipment needs: Questionnaires: Magill, Orrin R., 1944 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - YMCA Special Committee for the Study of Quarters and Equipment needs: Questionnaires: Medical College, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - YMCA Special Committee for the Study of Quarters and Equipment needs: Questionnaires: University Heights, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - YMCA Special Committee for the Study of Quarters and Equipment needs: Questionnaires: Washington Sqare, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Warner, C. Ford, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Series II: Questionnaires
  - Questionnaires - State & Federal Report, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires - State & Federal Report, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Questionnaires - State & Federal Report, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Questionnaires - State & Federal Report, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Questionnaires - State & Federal Report, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Questionnaires - State & Federal Report, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Questionnaires - State & Federal Report, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Questionnaires - State & Federal Report, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Questionnaires - State & Federal Report, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Questionnaires, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Questionnaires, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Questionnaires, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Questionnaires, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Questionnaires, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Questionnaires, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Questionnaires, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Worksheets for the Statistical Sections of the Office of Education Report, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Office of Education Questionnaire - Military status of Instructional Staff, Feb 1951 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - American Council on Education Questionnaire, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Office of Education Questionnaire - Federal Security Agency: Stats re: Reduction in Full Time Faculty, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Questionnaires, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Questionnaires, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Office of Education Questionnaire - Federal Security Agency Questionnaires, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - National Science Foundation, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Questionnaires, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Office of Education Questionnaire - Dept of Health, Education & Welfare Questionnaires, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Questionnaires, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Office of Education Questionnaire - Dept of Health, Education & Welfare Questionnaires, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Questionnaires, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Office of Education Questionnaire - Dept of Health, Education & Welfare Questionnaires, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Association for Urban Universities, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Questionnaires, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Office of Education Questionnaire - Dept of health, Education & Welfare Questionnaires, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Questionnaires, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Questionnaires, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Questionnaires, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - '"The World of Learning" Questionnaires, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Questionnaires, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Questionnaires, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Statistics, 1934-1940 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Statistics, 1940-1945 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Statistics, 1949-1957 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Series III: Law Center Campaign
  - Law Center Foundation, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bylaws of the Law Center Foundation, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Trustees of the Law Center Foundation, 1948-1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Law Center Dedication, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 63rd Annual Dinner of the NYU Law Alumni Association in honor of Hon. Anthony O. Savarse at 6valdorf, Apr 5, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - New York University Law Center Cornerstone celebration - Also Law Alumni, 62nd Annual Dinner at Waldorf and Minute presented to Vanderbilt by Council, Jan 31, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Law Alumni Association Dinner in honor of Arthur Vanderbilt at the Waldorf Astoria Hotel, Feb 10, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Judge Florence E. Allen Dinner, Nov 8, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - David Dudley Feild Centenary Dinner, Sep 30, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Law Campaign, Ramsey Corporation, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Law Campaign - Davella Mills Foundation, 1947-1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Law Campaign - Contributions to the Campaign, 1945-1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Law Campaign - Dinner, Conferment of Honorary Degrees, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Law Campaign - Dean Arthur Vanderbilt, 1945-1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Law Campaign - Correspondence with Council, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Law Campaign - Publicity, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)